<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Journey</string>
    <string name="title_activity_journey_home">Journey</string>
    <string name="start">Start Road Trip</string>
    <string name="join">Join Road Trip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_start_trip">Start Road Trip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_join_trip">Join Road Trip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_waypoint">Add Waypoint</string>
    <string name="waypoint">Add some Waypoint</string>
    <string name="distance_hint"><b>range(miles)</b></string>
    <string name="along_route_hint"><b>miles down route</b></string>
    <!--<string name="google_app_id">vertical-mapper-123021</string>-->
    <!--<string name="server_client_id">538969000595-85rg5ljc1bt4hfjith9kf4kjm2gsc3uf.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>-->
    <string name="server_client_id">538969000595-gh7i287c9p143fd1ageslnmj58bjg15r.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="use_current_loc_button">Use Current Location</string>

    <!-- Help screen -->
    <string name="help_title"><b><u>Journey Help</u></b></string>
    <string name="help_opening">
        Thank you for choosing Journey. This page will help you use Journey so that you can get the most out of it.
    </string>
    <string name="help_home_title"><b>Home Screen</b></string>
    <string name="help_home">
        The opening screen of Journey is a Map that centers on your current location. You can navigate the map just
        like you would navigate the map in Google Maps. From here, you can:\n
        1. Access the Navigation Drawer\n
        2. Start a new Road Trip\n
        3. Join a Road Trip that has already been set up
    </string>
    <string name="help_nav_title"><b>Navigation Drawer</b></string>
    <string name="help_nav">
        The Navigation Drawer contains pages that need to be easily accessible from the Home Screen. The Navigation
        Drawer contains the following pages:\n
        1. Login / Logout - Click this to either login or logout of Journey\n
        2. Settings - Use this page to change application settings, such as the maximum distance from your route that
        you would like to stop\n
        3. Help - This is the page you are currently on. This page contains information about using Journey\n
        4. About - The About page is a page created by us, the developers, so you can learn a bit more about us and
        about Journey
    </string>
    <string name="help_start_title"><b>Start Road Trip</b></string>
    <string name="help_start">
        The Start Road Trip page is where you will create the road trip that you would like to navigate. There are three
        important aspects to this page:\n
        1. Starting Destination - Enter the place you would like to start your road trip from\n
        2. Final Destination - Not the Super Smash Bros. map! Enter the place that you would like to end your road trip
        3. Caravan Trip - If you select this, your trip will become available for others to join. If you do this, once
        the trip starts you will be deemed the "Trip Admin", while everyone who joined your trip will be "Trip Passengers"
        (?)\n
        Once finished, press the Begin Road Trip button to start the road trip!
    </string>
    <string name="help_join_title"><b>Join Road Trip</b></string>
    <string name="help_join">
        The Join Road Trip page is where you will find a road trip, created by our application, to join.\n
        * Page WIP *
    </string>
    <string name="help_home_trip_title"><b>Trip Started</b></string>
    <string name="help_home_trip">
        Once you have either created or joined a trip, you will be brought back to the Home Screen (with the map), but
        there are a few different options now:\n
        1. Your route is displayed on the map as a line. * Additional info about route WIP *\n
        2. To add a stop to your route (Trip Admin) or request a stop (Trip Passenger), press the Add/Request Stop button\n
        \t<b>Note:</b> If you are driving, we advise you to use the voice control option so that you may focus on
        the road\n
        3. To use voice controls to add/request a route stop, press the microphone button on the right side of the display
        * Commands WIP *
    </string>
    <string name="help_add_request_stop_title"><b>Add/Request a Stop</b></string>
    <string name="help_add_request_stop">
        * Page WIP *
    </string>

    <!-- Join Trip -->
    <string name="join_trip_instruction">
        Please enter the email address of the person who created the trip below.
    </string>
    <string-array name="places_choices_array">
        <item>bar</item>
        <item>cafe</item>
        <item>campground</item>
        <item>car_repair</item>
        <item>car_wash</item>
        <item>convenience_store</item>
        <item>food</item>
        <item>gas_station</item>
        <item>hospital</item>
        <item>restaraunt</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
